Where Is Anne Frank is a animation, drama, family film directed by Ari Folman.
The film follows the journey of Kitty, the imaginary
friend to whom Anne Frank dedicated her diary.
A fiery teenager, Kitty wakes up in the near future in Anne Frank's house in Amsterdam and
embarks on a journey to find Anne, who she believes is still alive, in today's Europe.
While the young girl is shocked by the modern world,
she also comes across Anne's legacy.
Anne Frank (voice), played by Emily Carey.
Kitty (voice), played by Ruby Stokes.
Anne's Peter (voice), played by Sebastian Croft.
Kitty's Peter (voice), played by Ralph Prosser.
Otto Frank (voice), played by Michael Maloney.
Edith Frank (voice), played by Samantha Spiro.
Where Is Anne Frank is a 2021 animated magic realism film
directed by Israeli director Ari Folman.
The film follows Kitty, Anne Frank's imaginary friend to whom she
addressed her diary, manifesting in contemporary Amsterdam.
Seeking to learn what happened to her creator, Kitty attracts worldwide
attention and interacts with undocumented immigrants.
Where Is Anne Frank was shown out of competition at the
2021 Cannes Film Festival on 9 July 2021.
It was released in France on 8 December 2021 by Le Pacte, on 15 December 2021 in Belgium by
Cinéart, on 16 March 2022 in Luxembourg, and on 30 March 2022 in the Netherlands.
The tone is emotional.